Guide to the Neal Lane papers, 1998-2001, MS 502 MS 502
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series VI: Science & Technology (S & T) Conference, 2003; 161547
  - S & T Conference A List Invitations rsvp, 2003; 161550 (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - S & T Conference B List Invitations, 2003; 161551 (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - S & T Conference budget, 2003; 161552 (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - S & T Conference correspondence, 2003; 161553 (Box 91, Folder 20)
  - S & T Conference emails, 2003; 161617 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - S & T Conference final days (last 2 weeks), 2003; 161618 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - S & T Conference students, 2003; 161619 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - S & T Conference letters: A list, B list, NL students, 2003; 161620 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - S & T Conference letters: Seestrom, 2003; 161621 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - S & T Conference logistics, 2003; 161764 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - S & T Conference: Jack Marburger, 2003; 161765 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - S & T Conference meeting information, 2003; 161766 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - S & T Conference program (draft), 2003; 161767 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - S & T Conference publication: "Bridging the Gap between Science and Society", 2003; 161768 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - S & T Conference web page, 2003; 161769 (Box 92, Folder 11)
- Series VII: Presentations and lectures, 1993 - 2010; 161770
  - Symposium honoring the inauguration of Malcolm Gillis, 1993; 161771 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - NAS Workshop: "Scientific Communication and National Security", 2000; 161772 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Baker Institute: "Climate Change and its Impact", September 6, 2000; 162251 (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - URA Council Meeting: "URA Council of Presidents", January 31, 2001; 161774 (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Society of Rice University Women: "Science on Penmsylvania Avenue", February 11, 2001; 161775 (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - AAAS Meeting: "Grand Challenges of Nanotechnology", February 16, 2001; 161776 (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - AAAS: Nanotechnology, February 16, 2001; 161777 (Box 92, Folder 18)
  - Baker Institute Nuclear Conference: "Micro-Nuclear Reactors", March 19, 2001; 161778 (Box 92, Folder 19)
  - Ohio Statewide Trustees, March 21, 2001; 161779 (Box 92, Folder 20)
  - Ohio Statewide Trustees, March 21, 2001; 161780 (Box 92, Folder 21)
  - General Audiences: "Science on Pennsylvania Avenue", March 2001; 166346 (Box 92, Folder 22)
  - Branscomb Lecture: "Science on Pennsylvania Avenue", March 22, 2001; 161781 (Box 92, Folder 23)
  - AIP History of Physics luncheon, March 27, 2001; 161827 (Box 92, Folder 24)
  - Environmental Lunch Group: "Climate Change- Science, Policy, Politics", March 28, 2001; 161828 (Box 92, Folder 25)
  - Council on Competitiveness Summit, UCSD, April 5-6, 2001; 161829 (Box 92, Folder 26)
  - Ron Sass class: "Climate Change- Science, Policy, Politics", April 10, 2001; 161830 (Box 92, Folder 27)
  - Indo-US luncheon: Dronamraju, April 17, 2001; 161831 (Box 92, Folder 28)
  - IBM Almaden Institute: "The Grand Challenges of Nanotechnology", April 23-24, 2001; 161832 (Box 92, Folder 29)
  - Jim Tour class: Science and Technology Policy, April 26, 2001; 161833 (Box 92, Folder 30)
  - Chemistry graduate student career seminar, April 27, 2001; 164295 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - OSTP 25th Anniversary Symposium: MIT, May 1, 2001; 164296 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - AAAS Carey Lecture: "Talking turkey: Science, the economy, and the community", May 3, 2001; 164297 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Cornell Hartmanis Colloquium: regrets, May 5, 2001; 164298 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - CSSP: "Science inthe White House", May 7, 2001; 164299 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Global Air and Space International Business Forum, May 7-9, 2001; 164300 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Rice Society of Petroleum Engineers, May 10, 2001; 164301 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - AMS, APS, AAS Award, May 16, 2001; 164302 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - North Carolina State University honorary degree, May 19, 2001; 164303 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Los Alamos National Laboratory T-Division Review Committee, May 20-22, 2001; 164304 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - ICPEAC 2001 Conference: "International Space Policy and Atomic Collision Science", July 18, 2001; 164305 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - NRC Climate Workshop, August 12-13, 2001; 164306 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Rice Global Forum: "Role of Federal Science and Technology Policy in U.S. Competitiveness (Part I), September 4, 2001; 164307 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Rice Global Forum: "Role of Federal Science and Technology Policy in U.S. Competitiveness (Part II), September 4, 2001; 164308 (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - Physics Policy Committee Meeting agenda, September 6, 2001; 164309 (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Women's Club: "Science, Education, and Science Policy", September 12, 2001; 164310 (Box 93, Folder 16)
  - Bechtel Chief Engineers Conference: "21st Century Challenges", September 13, 2001; 164311 (Box 93, Folder 17)
  - International University of Bremen: Dialogue with Neal Lane and Winnaker, September 20, 2001; 164312 (Box 93, Folder 18)
  - River Oaks Breakfast Club: "Science on Pennsylvania Avenue", September 27, 2001; 164313 (Box 93, Folder 19)
  - Texas Christian University: "Science on Pennsylvania Avenue", October 7, 2001; 164314 (Box 93, Folder 20)
  - Romeo Club: "Science on Pennsylvania Avenue", October 12, 2001; 164315 (Box 93, Folder 21)
  - Houston Museum of Natural Science: "Some Views on Science, Policy, and the Public", October 16, 2001; 164316 (Box 93, Folder 22)
  - APS Laser Science DivisionAnnual Meeting: "Entrepreneurship in Science Policy", October 16, 2001; 164317 (Box 93, Folder 23)
  - Baker Institute Round Table DInner: "A View from Rice after Seven Years", October 18, 2001; 164318 (Box 93, Folder 24)
  - Tapia dinner: Remarks, October 19, 2001; 164319 (Box 93, Folder 25)
  - Notes for Allia's class, October 29, 2001; 164320 (Box 93, Folder 26)
  - Brito-Curl-Lane Faculty Lunch at CIPP, Baker Institute of Public Policy, November 6, 2001; 164321 (Box 93, Folder 27)
  - Asia Society Luncheon: "21st Century Challenges in Science, Engineering, and Technology", November 23, 2001; 164337 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Hong Kong Confernce: The New Golden Wealth triangle, November 23, 2001; 164339 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Chinese Academy of Sciences: "Issues in U. S. Science and Technology Policy" (Part I), November 27, 2001; 164344 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Chinese Academy of Sciences: "Issues in U. S. Science and Technology Policy" (Part II), November 27, 2001; 164345 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Nanotechnology and Environment Workshop: "Implications of Nanotechnology", December 10, 2001; 164346 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Letter of Recommendation for Dr. D. Allan Bromley, December 12, 2001; 164347 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Dinner at John and Ginger Sall home, December 15, 2001; 164348 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Brentwater Yacht and Country Club: "TheScience, Policy, and Politics of Climate Change", January 16, 2002; 164349 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Tokyo: "U.S. System of Support for Science and Technology R & D" - Cancelled, January 29, 2002; 164350 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Writing Across the Curriculum Conference: "What Leadership, Goals, and Policies Can Ensure that Students Communicate Well", February 23, 2002; 164351 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - University of Tulsa: "Science in Global Political Climate Change", February 27, 2002; 164352 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - University of Oklahoma: "A Three-Body Problem", March 1, 2002; 164353 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Iowa State: "Science and Society Dialogue", March 4, 2002; 164354 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Rice University Graduate Student Lecture: "A Three-Body Problem", March 18, 2002; 164355 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Nanotechnology Forum: Remarks to Nanotechnology Luncheon, March 21, 2002; 164356 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Air Force Association: "Science on Pennsylvania Avenue", March 24, 2002; 164357 (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Center for the Study of Cultures: " The Two Cultures - Plus One", April 2, 2002; 164358 (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - Rice Environmental Conference: Energy Deregulation Panel Discussion, April 6, 2002; 164359 (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - Tokyo, KEK: "U.S. System of Support for Science and Technology R & D" (Part I), April 11, 2002; 164360 (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Tokyo, KEK: "U.S. System of Support for Science and Technology R & D" (Part II), April 11, 2002; 164361 (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - University of California, Berkeley: "Science, Policy, and Politics- A Global Three - Body Problem", April 18, 2002; 164362 (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - Shell Lecture, Baker Institute for Public Policy - Introductory Remarks, April 25, 2002; 164363 (Box 94, Folder 22)
  - Shell Lecture, Baker Institute for Public Policy: "Societal Response to Climate Change" (Part I), April 25, 2002; 164364 (Box 94, Folder 23)
  - Shell Lecture, Baker Institute for Public Policy: "Societal Response to Climate Change" (Part II), April 25, 2002; 164365 (Box 94, Folder 24)
  - Rice School of Continuing Studies: "How much of our tax money should the federal government spend on research?", May 2, 2002; 164379 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Rice University Space Policy Workshop: "Introduction to Science and Engineering Education", May 5-7, 2002; 164382 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Rice - TMC Sigma Xi Awards Banquet: "Science, Policy, and Politics - A Harder Three - Body Problem", May 9, 2002; 164388 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - SUNY Albany Graduate Commencement: "Responsibilities in a Post 9/11 World", May 18, 2002; 164389 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - NNI Regional Workshop: Remarks, May 23, 2002; 164391 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Rice Board of Trustees: Remarks to Nanotechnology Session, May 23, 2002; 164392 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Remarks to Lord David Sainsbury at Rice, June 12, 2002; 164390 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Japan Society for the Promotion of Science: External Review (Part I), June 16 - 17, 2002; 164509 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Japan Society for the Promotion of Science: External Review (Part II), June 16 - 17, 2002; 164510 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Japan Society for the Promotion of Science: External Review (Part III), June 16 - 17, 2002; 164511 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Japan Society for the Promotion of Science: Science and Technology Basic Plan, June 2002; 164512 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Japan Society for the Promotion of Science: Round Table (Part I), June 2002; 164513 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Japan Society for the Promotion of Science: Round Table (Part II), June 2002; 164514 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Japan Society for the Promotion of Science: Exerpts from the JSPS Round Table, July 2002; 164515 (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - Japan Society for the Promotion of Science: Correspondence, Notes, July 2002; 164516 (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - Japan Society for the Promotion of Science: External Review report (final), 2002; 164517 (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - Japan Society for the Promotion of Science: NSF - Tokyo regional office materials, 2002; 164518 (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - REU Rice Summer Students Luncheon: "Presentation to REU", July 10, 2002; 164608 (Box 95, Folder 18)
  - Alliances for Graduate Education and Professionalism: "U.S. National Science Policies", July 19, 2002; 164609 (Box 95, Folder 19)
  - Medical Technology Leadership Forum: "Breaking Down the Barriers", July 21 - 22, 2002; 164610 (Box 95, Folder 20)
  - Baker Institute: "Introduction of Congressman Ralph Hall", August 26, 2002; 164611 (Box 95, Folder 21)
  - NSF Portrait Unveiling: "Comments at Portrait Unveiling", September 9, 2002; 164612 (Box 95, Folder 22)
  - U.T. Austin Deans Scholars Program: "Science on Pennsylvania Avenue", September 24 - 25, 2002; 164614 (Box 95, Folder 24)
  - Rice Alumni Leaders 2002 Conference: "The Two Cultures - Plus One", September 20, 2002; 164613 (Box 95, Folder 23)
  - Rice University Nanodays: "Welcoming Remarks", October 14 - 15, 2002; 164615 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Earth Science Graduate Student Seminar: "Some Views on Science, Policy, and Politics", October 19, 2002; 164616 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - U. K. Trade Mission at Rice: "Remarks to the U.K. Trade Mission", October 21, 2002; 164617 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Kansas State University: "Science in the White House" and "Physics Through Different Lenses", October 24, 2002; 164618 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - University of Michigan: "The Disconnect in Washington", November 7, 2002; 164619 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Sloan Seminar: "Perspective on the U. S. Distributed System of Science and Technology", November 11, 2002; 164620 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Rice Chemistry Graduate Students: "Perspective on the U. S. Distributed System of Science and Technology", November 13, 2002; 164621 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Georgia State University: "Science, Policy, and Politics: A Complicated Three - Body Problem", November 19, 2002; 164622 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Sigma Xi Forum: "Introductory Remarks", November 14, 2002; 164623 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Science and Technology Advisory Group: "A Perspective on the U. S. Distributed System of Science and Technology", December 2, 2002; 164624 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - The National Nanotechnology Initiative: "From the Atomic to the Nanoscale" Conference, December 13, 2002; 164625 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - American Physical Society: "A Perspective on the National Nanotechnology Initiative (NNI)", December 13 - 14, 2002; 164626 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - CBEN - Rice Alliance: "The Politics of Space Exploration", January 24, 2003; 164627 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - National Academies Committee on Science, Engineering, and Public Policy: "Statement", February 2003; 164628 (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - Columbia Disaster, February 1, 2003; 164629 (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - Nobel Exhibit Opening Dinner: "Comments at Nobel Exhibit", February 3, 2003; 164630 (Box 96, Folder 16)
  - Rice Curl/Brito Class: "Remarks", February 11, 2003; 164631 (Box 96, Folder 17)
  - Rice University Scholars Program Seminar: "Lord Snow's 'Two Cultures' ", February 18. 2003; 164632 (Box 96, Folder 18)
  - Nano Ventures 2003: "A Policy Perspective on Nanotechnology", February 28, 2003; 164633 (Box 96, Folder 19)
  - Iowa State University: "Fifty Years after Snow's "Two Cultures" ", March 4, 2003; 164634 (Box 96, Folder 20)
  - Physics Policy Committee (PPC): Meeting Minutes, March 8, 2003; 164635 (Box 96, Folder 21)
  - Euroscience/ESOF 2004 Discussion: "A U. S. Perspective on Nanotechnology", March 19, 2003; 164636 (Box 96, Folder 22)
  - Texas Higher Education Summit: Meeting Information, March 25 - 26, 2003; 164637 (Box 96, Folder 23)
  - Fondren Dinner: "Comments", April 2, 2003; 164638 (Box 96, Folder 24)
  - Rice University/ Monterrey Tech Explorations: "Rice Perspectives", April 2, 2003; 164639 (Box 96, Folder 25)
  - Rice University: "Achieving Societal Benefits from Science and Engineering Discoveries", April 7, 2003; 164640 (Box 96, Folder 26)
  - American Physical Society: " The Founding Father of Civic Science", April 7, 2003; 164641 (Box 96, Folder 27)
  - Anthropology 298: " Discussion of Technology and Public Policy", April 9, 2003; 164642 (Box 96, Folder 28)
  - Houston Museum of Natural Science: "The Noble Challenge", April 15, 2003; 164643 (Box 96, Folder 29)
  - Electrical Engineering 391: "Lecture", April 16, 2003; 164644 (Box 96, Folder 30)
  - Scientia: Business Meeting, April 17, 2003; 164645 (Box 96, Folder 31)
  - Gershon Sher visit, April 18, 2003; 164646 (Box 96, Folder 32)
  - Medical Technology Leadership Forum: Panel, April 28, 2003; 164647 (Box 96, Folder 33)
  - RIce - BIPP Nano-Energy Conference: "Dean Kamen Introduction", May 2 - 4, 2003; 164673 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Rice Space Institute: "Introduction of Chris Kirchhoff", May 7, 2003; 164674 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - American Meteorological Society: "Amateur's Perspective of Science, Policy, and Politics", June 9, 2003; 164675 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - U.S. - Mexico (Rice/Monterrey Tech) Conference: "Comments", June 26 - 27, 2003; 164676 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Texas Common Sense: "Organizational Workshop Information", August 20, 2003; 164677 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Packard Fellows Colloquium: "Bridging the Gap", September 6, 2003; 164678 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - BIPP - American Academy of Arts & Sciences Space Policy Workshop: "Commercial Perspectives on Space Development", Sepember 17 -18, 2003; 164679 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Rice University Nano Days Conference: "A Personal View of Nanotechnology", October 12, 2003; 164680 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Meeting with the House Science Committee notes, October 20, 2003; 164681 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - APS/PPC meeting information, October 21, 2003; 164682 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - American Chemical Society: "Symposium Overview", October 26 - 28, 2003; 164683 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Fondren Library/Woodson Research Center: "Benjamin Franklin - The Founding Father of Civic Science", November 6, 2003; 164684 (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Smalley - Curl - CNST Celebration Innovation: "Celebration Script", November 13, 2003; 164685 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - SE Regional Meeting, American Chemical Society: "Some problems with Federal Science and Technology Policy", November 14, 2003; 164686 (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - First Presbyterian Church study group: "Fifty Years after Snow's 'Two Cultures' ", November 23, 2003; 164687 (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - BIPP - Space Policy panel: "Introductory Remarks", December 11, 2003; 164688 (Box 97, Folder 16)
  - McCain Senate Space Committee: "Oral Statement", January 27 - 28, 2004; 164689 (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - U. S. Senate: "NASA Presentation", January 28, 2004; 164690 (Box 97, Folder 18)
  - Scientia Talk: "Things that go 'Click' in the Night", February 17, 2004; 164691 (Box 97, Folder 19)
  - Jefferson Davis Society meeting: "Comments", February 18, 2004; 164692 (Box 97, Folder 20)
  - National Academies meeting with the Business Council: "Remarks", February 19, 2004; 164693 (Box 97, Folder 21)
  - Rice University Alumni Course: "Albert Einstein: Lost in Space-Time", March 12, 2004; 164694 (Box 97, Folder 22)
  - Case Media Fellowship: "Societal Implications of Nanotechnology", March 16, 2004; 164695 (Box 97, Folder 23)
  - Rice University: "Fifty Years after Snow's 'Two Cultures' ", March 16, 2004; 164696 (Box 97, Folder 24)
  - American Physical Society meeting: "Freedom, Openness, and International Cooperation", March 22 - 26, 2004; 164697 (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Fotofest: "State of Water in the World", April 2, 2004; 164698 (Box 97, Folder 26)
  - Baker Institute Student Forum: "Civic Science - National Imperative", April, 7, 2004; 164699 (Box 97, Folder 27)
  - U. T. Health Science Center: "Why should society invest in research?", April 14, 2004; 164700 (Box 97, Folder 28)
  - Rice School of Continuing Studies: "The Politics of Space Exploration", April 26, 2004; 164795 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Sante Fe Institute: "Searching for Order in Science Policy", May 8, 2004; 164796 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - AAAS Science and Technology Policy: " A Few Words about Energy", May 13, 2004; 164797 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Symposium in Honor of John Holdren: "Thoughts on Science, Policy, and Politics", May 22, 2004; 164798 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - DAMOP Banquet: "AMO Physics and the Facts of Life", May 27, 2004; 164799 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Aspen Institute: "Report", June 23, 2004; 164800 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Alliance for Graduate Education and the Professoriate: "Bridging the Gap between Science and Society", July 30, 2004; 164801 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Aspen Conference: three panel discussions (Part I), August 8-11, 2004; 164802 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Aspen Conference: three panel discussions (Part II), August 8-11, 2004; 164803 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Los Alamos National Laboratory: "Bridging the Gap between Science and Society", August 12, 2004; 164804 (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Euroscience Forum: "The Birth of the U.S. National Nanotechnology Initiative (NNI)", August 26, 2004; 164805 (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Women's Club: "Integrity in Science", September 8, 2004; 164806 (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Shell Center for Sustainability: "Remarks", September 14, 2004; 164807 (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Panel - Lord Julian Hunt: "Comments following Julian Hunt", October 4, 2004; 164808 (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - AAAS Induction Ceremony Meeting Information, October 9, 2004; 164809 (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - Rice School of Continuing Studies: "The Birth of the U.S. NNI", October 13, 2004; 164810 (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - BIPP Nano-Energy Tech notes, October 15-17, 2004; 164811 (Box 98, Folder 17)
  - Society of Environmental Journalists: "Science and Politics", October 20-24, 2004; 164812 (Box 98, Folder 18)
  - CBEN External Advisory Board: "Letter Report of First Meeting of CBEN EAB", October 29, 2004; 164813 (Box 98, Folder 19)
  - Jim Tours Honors Organic Chemistry class: "Comments on U.S. Science, Policy, and Politics", November 12, 2004; 164814 (Box 98, Folder 20)
  - BIPP/Stem Cell Conference: "Morality vs. Mortality" (Part I), November 20-21, 2004; 164815 (Box 98, Folder 21)
  - BIPP/Stem Cell Conference: "Morality vs. Mortality" (Part II), Novemerb 20-21, 2004; 164816 (Box 98, Folder 22)
  - Hong Kong University of Science and Technology: "Introduction" and "The Birth of the U.S. NNI", December 3, 2004; 164817 (Box 98, Folder 23)
  - Symposium for Jim Krumhansl: "Jim Krumhansl- Model Civic Scientist", January 12, 2005; 164818 (Box 98, Folder 24)
  - Coastal Cities Conference: "Welcome Remarks", February 9, 2005; 164819 (Box 98, Folder 25)
  - Houston Chronicle Briefing, February 14, 2005; 164820 (Box 98, Folder 26)
  - Rice/Pew Center on Global Climate Change: "U.S. Energy Scenarios for the 21st Century", February 16, 2005; 164821 (Box 98, Folder 27)
  - AAAS Annual Meeting, Washington, DC: "Physics in the National Interest", February 20, 2005; 164822 (Box 98, Folder 28)
  - University of Colorado at Colorado Springs: "One Perspective on U.S. Science & Technology Policy", February 24, 2005; 164830 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - BIPP Student Forum/Mock Senate Hearing, February 28, 2005; 164831 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Rice Sloan Masters Seminar: "One Person's Perspective on U.S. Science & Technology", March 21, 2005; 164832 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Rice Undergraduate Scholars Program (RUSP) Seminar: "One Person's Perspective on U.S. Science & Technology", March 22, 2005; 164833 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - University of Oklahoma: "Perspective on American Science & Technology Policy", March 24, 2005; 164834 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - University of South Carolina: "Origins of Nanotech Policy: Inside Story", March 31, 2005; 164835 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - University of Chicago Colloquium: "One Perspective on American Science - Some Trouble Ahead", April 14-15, 2005; 164836 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - U.T. Board of Regents: " On Los Alamos National Laboratory", April 28, 2005; 164837 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Our Common Future Ron Sass Symposium: "Commitment of a Civic Scientist", May 9, 2005; 164838 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Baker Institute/Rice Space Science Institute Talk: "Introduction of David McKay and Everett Gibson", May 10, 2005; 164839 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - GPI- Advocacy Conference: "Remarks", June 11, 2005; 164840 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - U.S. Civilian Research and Development Foundation: "International Science & Technology Collaborations can Advance U.S. Government Policy", June 14-16, 2005; 164841 (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Kirtland AFB: "U.S. Science & Technology: The View from 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue", June 21, 2005; 164842 (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - Aspen Institute: "Threats to the Future of U.S. Science & Technology", July 11-13, 2005; 164843 (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - University of Texas Medical Branch (UTMB): "Trends in Science Policy - Some Storm Clouds on the Horizon", July 15, 2005; 164844 (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - Rice AGEP Colleagues: "Trends in Science Policy- Some Storm Clouds on the Horizon", July 29, 2005; 164845 (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - BIPP Student Forum Reception: "Comments", September 8, 2005; 164887 (Box 99, Folder 17)